[Home](https://www.wefi.com/) Solutions SDKs Analytics News

Back [Wi-Fi Offload](https://www.wefi.com/wifi-offload) [Sports Venues](https://www.wefi.com/sports-venues) [Enterprise](https://www.wefi.com/enterprise) [IoT Connected Cars](https://www.wefi.com/connected-cars) [Location Data](https://www.wefi.com/location-data) [Amenity Wi-Fi Network](https://www.wefi.com/amenity-network)

Back [Connectivity & Offload](https://www.wefi.com/connectivity-offload) [Data Collection](https://www.wefi.com/data-collection) [IoT](https://www.wefi.com/iot) [Find Wifi](https://www.wefi.com/find-wifi)

Back [Networks](https://www.wefi.com/networks) [Venue Analytics](https://www.wefi.com/venue-analytics)

Back [Blog](https://www.wefi.com/blog) [Events](https://www.wefi.com/events)

PRIVACY policy
==============

### **Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Privacy Policy for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.

WeFi offers several software solutions and services. References to WeFi’s products in this Privacy Policy include WeFi’s mobile application and SDK, analytics services and website.

This Privacy Policy applies to our interactions with you and each of our products and services that reference or link to this Policy.

We reserve the right to update or make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion without prior notice, which changes we may provide to you by any reasonable means, including without limitation, by posting the revised version of this Privacy Policy on our website at [www.wefi.com/privacy](http://www.wefi.com/privacy). You can determine when this Policy was last revised by referring to the “Last updated” legend at the top of this Privacy Policy.

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will become effective upon our posting of the revised version on our website as mentioned. Except where your separate consent is required by law, your use of our products constitutes your acceptance of the revised Policy then in effect.

By using our products which link to or reference this Privacy Policy, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy, please do not use such products.

### **The Type of Data We Collect**

The application collects data to operate effectively and to furnish or enhance your experience with our products. You will not have to provide any personal information such as name, contact information, payment data or demographics when using our products. Nevertheless, while using the products, we will record data pertaining to your interaction with our products such as device performance, location, cellular quality, Wi-Fi and internet quality. This is so as ensure best performance and quality of the service provided. The data is collected and kept hashed and anonymized and is statistically processed to prevent tracking individual details.

You have choices about the data we collect. When you are asked to provide acceptance to permissions, you may decline. However, if you choose not to provide permissions that are crucial for the provision a service or a feature, you may not be able to use that service or feature or its performance may be degraded.

### **Location Information**

We collect details about your current location both when the application is visible and, if permission is granted, when in the background. This information is used to find access points near you, help guide you to their locations and aids us in identifying and connecting to those points. You may decline permission for background access to location. However, this will severely limit the ability of the application to find and connect to optimal points.

### **How We Use Collected Data**

We only collect data required for products functionality. Before or at the time of collecting information, we clearly identify the purpose or purposes for which the information is being collected.

We collect and use information solely for the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by product functionality and compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

We will collect information by permissions and lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge and consent of the individual concerned.

The data collected will be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, will be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

### **How We Protect Your Data**

We use commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected. However, no security system is impenetrable, and we cannot guarantee the security of our systems 100%. In the event of any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take all reasonable steps to investigate the situation and, where appropriate, to notify what information may have been compromised, and to take such action as may be required by applicable laws and regulations.

We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

### **GDPR Compliance**  

### **Collection and Sharing of Location Information**

In addition to other information described in this policy, we may collect and share with third party ad and data networks precise location information. This location information may be used by itself, aggregated, or combined with mobile identifiers (such as IDFAs and Android IDs), and shared with third parties for purposes related to advertising, analytics, attribution (e.g., measuring ad performance), analytics and market research. You can remove your consent to having your location data collected by changing the settings on your device. (Certain services may lose functionality as a result.) You can “opt out” of various third party uses of Apple’s and Android’s advertising identifiers through those platforms’ corresponding device settings, as well.

**Special Note Regarding the Use of our Products by Children:** Our products are not directed to children under the age of 16.  Although our product do not require invoking any personal information, if you are under the age of 16, please do not provide personal data in connection with your use of Wefi’s products, services and website. We encourage parents and guardians to go online with their children whenever using any of our products and services.

**Solutions**

**SDKs**

**Analytics**

**News**

© 2020 Wefi, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
